<!--
  ~ PROJECT LICENSE
  ~
  ~ This project was submitted by Gehad Ahmed as part of the Nanodegree At Udacity.
  ~
  ~ As part of Udacity Honor code, your submissions must be your own work, hence
  ~ submitting this project as yours will cause you to break the Udacity Honor Code and the suspension of your account.
  ~
  ~ Me, the author of the project, allow you to check the code as a reference, but if you submit it, it's your own responsibility if you get expelled.
  ~
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018 Gehad Ahmed
  ~
  ~ Besides the above notice, the following license applies and this license notice must be included in all works derived from this project.
  ~
  ~ MIT License
  ~
  ~ Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  ~ of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  ~ in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  ~ to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  ~ copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  ~ furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
  ~
  ~ The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
  ~
  ~ THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  ~ IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  ~ FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  ~ AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  ~ LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  ~ OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
  ~ SOFTWARE.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cairo Tour Guide</string>

    <!--Tabs Titles-->
    <string name="category_Attractions">Historic</string>
    <string name="category_Parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_Restaurants">Diners</string>
    <string name="category_Activities">To-Do</string>

    <!--Attractions Titles, Descriptions and Addresses-->
    <string name="Attr1_title">The Great Pyramids of Giza</string>
    <string name="Attr1_Descrp">The Great Pyramid of Giza is a defining symbol
        of Egypt and the last of the ancient Seven Wonders of the World.
        It is located on the Giza plateau near the modern city of Cairo and was
        built over a twenty-year period during the reign of the king Khufu.</string>
    <string name="Attr1_Address">Al-Haram, Giza, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Attr2_title">The Egyptian Museum</string>
    <string name="Attr2_Descrp">The Egyptian Museum is home to an extensive
        collection of ancient Egyptian antiquities. It has 120,000 items,
        with a representative amount on display, the remainder in storerooms.
        The edifice is one of the largest museums in the region.</string>
    <string name="Attr2_Address">Qasr an Nile, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Attr3_title">The Saladin Citadel</string>
    <string name="Attr3_Descrp">i.	The Saladin Citadel of Cairo is a medieval
        Islamic fortification in Cairo, Egypt. The location, on Mokattam hill
        near the center of Cairo, was once famous for its fresh breeze and
        grand views of the city. It is now a preserved historic site, with mosques and museums.
        In 1976, it was proclaimed by UNESCO as a part of the World Heritage Site.</string>
    <string name="Attr3_Address">Qesm Al Khalifah, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Attr4_title">Sultan Hassan Mosque</string>
    <string name="Attr4_Descrp">i.	The Sultan Hassan Mosque is a massive mosque and school
        located in the Old city of Cairo, it was built during the Mamluk Islamic era in Egypt.
        At the time of construction the mosque was considered remarkable for its fantastic size
        and innovative architectural components. </string>
    <string name="Attr4_Address">El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <!--Parks Titles, Descriptions and Addresses-->
    <string name="Park1_title">Al-Azhar Park</string>
    <string name="Park1_Descrp">Al-Azhar Park is a public park located in Cairo, Egypt.
        Among several honors, this park is listed as one of the world\'s
        sixty great public spaces by the Project for Public Spaces (PPS).
        It’s commanding stunning panoramic views of the world's most intriguing city.
        Al-Azhar Park offers every visitor a glimpse into the captivating past. </string>
    <string name="Park1_Address">El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Park2_title">Japanese Garden</string>
    <string name="Park2_Descrp">The Japanese gardens are a feature of the town (Helwan).
        They must have been laid out years ago but they are still lovely containing
        as they do a number of fish ponds, numerous walks which are surmounted by arbours,
        which are or rather were probably used as tea garden shelters from the sun</string>
    <string name="Park2_Address">Fayzi St., Helwan, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Park3_title">International Park</string>
    <string name="Park3_Descrp">This park has International in its name because some
        of its flowers, trees, and animals originate from different countries around the world.
        One of its entrances has flags of the countries that are represented in the garden.</string>
    <string name="Park3_Address">Nasr City, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Park4_title">Gabalaya Garden</string>
    <string name="Park4_Descrp">The Aquarium Grotto Garden—also called El Gabalaya Garden
        after the name of the street where it is located Unique for its architectural beauty,
        the garden’s formations are made of clay to look like fish gills. The Aquarium Grotto Garden
        has many underground grottoes that used to host various unique types of
        fish from the Nile and other places.</string>
    <string name="Park4_Address">Al-Gabalayah, Zamalek, Giza, Egypt</string>

    <!--Restaurants Titles, Descriptions and Addresses-->
    <string name="Rest1_title">Chili’s Nile City</string>
    <string name="Rest1_Descrp">i.	Chili\'s Grill is an American casual dining restaurant chain
        that features Tex-Mex-style cuisine. You can enjoy having your lunch/dinner
        while enjoying the fabulous view of the Nile river and the nice atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="Rest1_Address">Nile City, Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Rest2_title">Bab Al-Qasr Kempinski</string>
    <string name="Rest2_Descrp">An oriental cuisine infused with Egyptian and Levant flavours
        and subtle combination of spices. Bab Al Qasr sets the stage for an authentic dinner
        in ambient surroundings, accented with belly dance performances on selected nights.</string>
    <string name="Rest2_Address">First Settlement, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Rest3_title">Sheikh Al-Arab Village</string>
    <string name="Rest3_Descrp">Above the central plateau of Al-Mokattam mountain, you can enjoy
        the grilled and barbecued meat and chicken made by an innovative way taken from
        the Bedouin people called "Al-Mandi"</string>
    <string name="Rest3_Address">Central plateau, Al-Mokattam, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Rest4_title">Al-Dahan </string>
    <string name="Rest4_Descrp">You can enjoy the variety of Grilled meat and chickens along side
        the great atmosphere in the heart of the historical places and mosques</string>
    <string name="Rest4_Address">El-Gamaleya, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <!--Activities Titles, Descriptions and Addresses-->
    <string name="Act1_title">Nile Cruise</string>
    <string name="Act1_Descrp">You can enjoy having a cruise in the Nile river and watching the
    monuments like Cairo Tower with some fresh air and nice atomsphere</string>
    <string name="Act1_Address">Qasr an Nile, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Act2_title">Sandboarding</string>
    <string name="Act2_Descrp">Sandboarding is a boardsport and extreme sport. It is a recreational
        activity and takes place on sand dunes. It involves riding across or down a dune while standing
        with both feet strapped to a board. Sandboarding can also be practised sitting down
        or lying on the belly or the back. </string>
    <string name="Act2_Address">Gaber Ibn Hayan St., Dokki, Giza, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Act3_title">Escape Room</string>
    <string name="Act3_Descrp">Like Crystal Maze in the 90’s, our rooms will provide
        an interactive experience where teams race against time to ESCAPE the room by finding clues
        based on various scenarios to solve live puzzles within 60 minutes. We have designed
        the experience to appeal to different age groups and all backgrounds.</string>
    <string name="Act3_Address">Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt</string>

    <string name="Act4_title">Bubble Football</string>
    <string name="Act4_Descrp">A new funny version of Football games, as you wear a huge
        transparent plastic ball along with your team and start bumping and bouncing
        with a lot of laughing.</string>
    <string name="Act4_Address">Sheraton, Cairo, Egypt</string>
</resources>
